情况不妙 Torres和McGee应该怎么办呢
This is bad. What are Torres and McGee supposed to do?
-说实话 -嗯 这很糟 对吧
- Tell the truth. - Yeah, that's bad, right?
Hartgrave呢 他在哪儿
Hartgrave, where is he?
根据公司的安全记录 他刚刚打了卡
According to company security, he just clocked in.
-好 我们走 -好的
- Okay, let's go. - Okay.
可能也没那么糟
Maybe it's not that bad.
那是美国国防部长
That's the United States Secretary of Defense.
-我们走 -他现在都搞上门拜访那一套了吗
- Let's go. - He's making house calls now?
嗯 情况不妙
Yeah, it's bad.
先生们
Gentlemen,
等我一会儿 Vance主任
Give me a minute. Director Vance.
Crawford部长 我想
Secretary Crawford. I'd like to...
NCIS不仅仅违背了一个直接的命令
Not only did NCIS disobey a direct order,
你们还黑进了绝密的政府记录
you hacked classified government records.
这两个是涉事的探员吗
Are these the agents responsible?
我就说一句 如果知道密码还算黑吗
I mean, is it hacking if you had the password?
交出武器和警徽 马上
Weapons and badges, now.
Vance主任 我要终止你的调查
Director Vance, I'm shutting down your investigation.
至于特别探员
And as for Special Agents
McGee和Torres
McGee and Torres,
你们俩得去监狱了
you two are going to prison.
Toil and Trouble Original Air Date on January 8, 2019
翻译 素时 42 柒九一九 二噁英 小飞 鸡血
校对  小飞  二噁英
主校 Vincent
分配 鸡血
== sync, corrected by elderman == @elder_man
Leon NCIS有没有违背我的命令
Leon, did NCIS disobey my order?
部长先生 我自己还在了解情况中
Mr. Secretary, I'm playing catch-up myself.
-你的特别探员有没有犯罪 -我知道情况看起来不妙
- Did your agents commit a crime? - I agree it looks bad.
但是不意味着有人犯了罪
Doesn't always mean that there's a crime.
-我来这儿不是为了听悲伤的故事的 -你是来问答案的
- I'm not here for sad stories. - You're here for answers.
联邦机构违法了 我得赶在
A federal agency breaking the law? I have to get
全国的媒体知道之前解决这事儿
ahead of this before it breaks to national media.
那我们就保证将它妥善解决
Then let's make sure we get it right.
我们都想知道事实
We both want the truth.
当然了 你是在说
Damn Skippy. Are you suggesting
这后头还有什么无懈可击的原因吗
there's a perfectly good reason for this?
我什么都没说
I'm not saying a damn word,
但是McGee和Torres探员
but Agents McGee and Torres
会很乐意解释一下这一切
will be happy to explain,
从头开始 一个细节都不落
from the beginning, in great detail.
我们的生死就取决于此了吗
As if our necks depended on it?
是的 没错
Oh, they do, son.
Nick 不如你先开始吧
Nick, why don't you start?
-什么 -对
- What? - Yeah.
-为什么是我 -因为在研讨会的那个人是你
- Why me? - You were the one at the seminar.
是你非得让我去的
Only because you made me go in your place.
嗯 因为我级别比你高
Yeah, I had seniority.
先生们 什么研讨会
Gentlemen, what seminar?
执法舆情学
"Optics In Law Enforcement."
两天前在弗里蒙特酒店
Two days ago at the Freemont Inn.
太无聊了 是不是
So boring, am I right?
培训是我的主意
That training was my idea.
唔
Mm...
我是说 开始的时候
I mean, like, boring...
是有一点无聊啦
at first...
这份录像是由邻居拍摄
This footage was taken by a neighbor,
在发布到社交媒体上后
and after being posted to social media,
有人开始质疑FBI的突袭战术
some are now calling FBI raid tactics into question.
好 在我们开始讨论之前 我想要感谢
Okay, before we discuss, I'd like to thank
我们的媒体专门小组
our media panelists for joining us
在为期三天的研讨会的第一天加入我们
on the first day of our three-day seminar.
现在 在观看了新闻剪辑之后
Now, after watching that news clip,
有人想要分享一下 我们作为联邦探员
can someone suggest what we, as federal agents,
还能怎样做得更好吗
could do better?
第一 根本别给FBI打电话
For starters, never call the FBI.
有人吗
Anyone?
可以从我们工作的
This could relate to any aspect
-任何方面来讲哦 -哈
- of our job. - Huh.
两个小时以内你得收了起码40条短信了吧
That's, like, 40 texts in less than two hours.
你还数了啊
You've been counting?
又没别的事儿可干
There's nothing else to do
因为这些我都知道了
'cause I know all this.
我不知道的是他的名字
What I don't know is his name.
谁的名字
Whose name?
哦 那个明天晚上要跟你约会的人的
Oh, the guy you're going on a date tomorrow night.
好了好了 别再看我手机屏幕了 他的名字叫Boyd
All right, stop looking at my screen, and his name is Boyd.
-他还在这儿呢 -是的 第五次约会了
- He's still around? - Yeah. It's date number five.
你还数了啊
You're counting now?
-你还好吗 -我好无聊啊
- Are you okay? - I'm bored.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
而且 我们都不应该来这儿的
Plus, we're not even supposed to be here.
你有什么要补充的吗 特别探员
Something you'd like to add, Special Agent...
McGee
McGee?
没 不用了
Nah, I'm good.
我要求所有人都关掉手机的
I asked for all cell phones to be turned off.
真抱歉 是McGee探员的
I am so sorry, it belongs to Agent McGee.
我一直都在告诉他 警察要工作好
I keep telling him that good police work
就得从集中注意开始
starts with being fully attentive.
没错 谢谢你
Exactly. Thank you,
-Gibbs探员 -不用谢
- Agent Gibbs. - You are very welcome.
哦 哦 不 是我 是我
Oh. Oh, no, it's my, it's my
女儿的学校 出事儿了
daughter's school. There's been an accident.
对不起 我得走了
I-I'm sorry, I have to go.
天呐 他没事儿吧
Oh, my word. Will he be all right?
我真不知道
You know what? I don't really know.
我去看看 抱歉
I'm gonna go check. I'm so sorry.
好了 回到我们手头的任务
Okay, back to the task at hand:
执法舆情学
optics in law enforcement.
干得好 老大
Nice job, boss.
嗯 你也是 女儿那个事儿真是神来之笔
Yeah, you, too. The daughter thing was a nice touch.
我跟你说 Gibbs和McGee可是欠我们很大个人情
Hey, let me tell you something, Gibbs and McGee owe us big time.
好吧 级别高也不能这么干
Okay, that's not exactly how seniority works.
嗯 再来两天我可忍不了
Yeah, I can't take two more days of this.
噢 听起来像个派对
Ooh, sounds like a party.
嗯 Clutterbuck先生及太太 Ned和Charlene
Yeah, Mrs. And Mr. Ned and Charlene Clutterbuck.
我来的时候看见了
I read it when we came in.
时代的爱情故事
A love story for the ages.
嗯 就像Ellie和Boyd
Yeah, like Ellie and Boyd.
我可是要饿死了 不知道Clutterbucks的婚礼有没有自助餐
Well, I'm starving. I wonder if the Clutterbucks have a buffet.
我们去看看 你可以假装是 呃 时髦的远亲
Let's find out. You can be the, uh, the stylish distant cousin
我可以假装是坏男孩型的男朋友
and I can be the bad-boy boyfriend.
嗨 里面的人都还好吗
Hello? Everybody okay in here?
我的天 不
Oh, my God, no!
看起来新郎和新娘
Whoo, looks like the bride and the groom
有点迫不及待了
are getting an early start.
是伴郎和伴娘
Yeah, try the best man and the maid of honor.
不重要 Phil 我觉得他死了
It doesn't matter, Phil. I think he's dead.
什么 好吧 慢一点 谁 谁死了
Wha-- Okay, slow down. Who-Who's dead?
我们没做错什么 好吗
Look, we didn't do anything wrong, okay?
我们就是想找个安静点的地方
We just came in here to get some peace and quiet.
你裤子穿反了
Your pants are on backwards.
我们撞到一张桌子 我对上帝发誓
W-We bumped into a table and I swear to God
有一具尸体掉下来了 就在后面
a body fell off of it. It's back there.
好吧 你们为什么不去外面等呢
All right, look, why don't you guys just wait outside?
-嗯 -我去看看灯在哪儿
- Yeah. - I'll look for the lights.
-好 -我们要不要找个卫生间
- Okay. - Should we find a bathroom?
我已经没心情了
I'm not in the mood anymore.
里头好冷
It's freezing in here.
哇 这儿有一具尸体
Whoa. I got a body.
呃 更像个坟场
Ugh. More like a graveyard.
嗯 这自助餐不对啊
Yeah, this is the wrong kind of buffet.
嗯 我也不咋饿了
Yeah, I'm not so hungry anymore.
别等我 继续
Don't wait for me. Continue.
或许你想让我把房间调成SCIF模式
Perhaps you'd like to me to put the room in SCIF mode, sir,
这样我们就不会被打扰了
so we won't be disturbed.
没必要 Leon 我就是在跟外头的属下说
No need, Leon. I was just telling my people outside
我马上就好
I won't be much longer.
我还没听到任何
I have yet to hear
能让我改主意的事
anything that changes my mind.
这可能有帮助
This might help.
请坐
Sit down, please.
不用了 我还是站着吧
Oh, no thanks, I'd rather stand.
对循环和呼吸好
It's better for circulation and breathing.
-你没得选 坐下 -我在看什么
- Wasn't an option. Sit down. - What am I looking at?
这是我们审讯室的闭路电视
It's a closed-circuit feed from our interrogation room.
这个嫌疑人是一个正在进行中的
This suspect is the key to an investigation
-调查的关键人物 -他是谁
- already in full swing. - Who is he?
能帮助我们阻止恐怖袭击的人
The man who will help us prevent an act of terrorism.
恐怖主义 你们能证明吗
Terrorism? You can prove that?
McGee探员 Torres探员
Agents McGee, Torres.
宾馆里的尸体
The bodies at the hotel.
对
Right.
好了 别围在这里 你们都是联邦探员
All right, keep clear. You are all Federal agents.
-你们知道该怎么做 -大伙们
- You know how this works. - Everyone,
请自行回到研讨会去
please make your way back to the seminar.
或者留下来 跟NCIS学学怎么办事儿 宝贝
Or stay and NCIS will show you how it's done, baby.
显然你的女儿感觉好多了
Clearly your daughter's feeling better.
拜托 大伙
Come on, people.
把这里弄成犯罪现场
Making this a crime scene
非常草率 Gibbs探员
was very premature, Agent Gibbs.
你的探员制造了不必要的混乱
Your agents created chaos for nothing.
-看起来不是完全没必要 -这家酒店
- Doesn't look like nothing. - This hotel
只以最高标准和等级运行
operates with only the highest standards and class.
Richard
Richard!
嗯
Um...
我九分钟前就跟你要了
I asked for this nine minutes ago.
如你所见
As you can see,
这里有医学会议
there's a medical conference starting in here
明早开始
tomorrow morning.
欧 手术机器人
Oh, surgical robots?
会议由制作它们的公司赞助
The conference is sponsored by the company that makes them.
与会者将能够
The attendees will be able
在这里测试机器人
to test the robots right here.
-在尸体上 -所以他们是医学尸体
- On the bodies. - Making them medical cadavers,
不是被谋杀的受害者
not murder victims.
所以我们能在媒体把这里变成某种
So can we wrap this up before the media gets wind
Jonestown惨案的续集之前赶紧完事么
【注：1978年11月18日，美国邪教组织“人民圣殿教”的信徒在教主吉姆·琼斯的胁迫下
在南美洲圭亚那琼斯镇（Jonestown）集体自杀。】
and turns this into some kind of Jonestown sequel?
太迟了 电视台的老Ross已经在隔壁了
Too late. Guy Ross was already next door.
他想采访一下
He's looking for an interview.
这里没有违法行为
There's nothing illegal here.
这20个医学尸体都是合法的
These 20 medical cadavers are completely legal.
我们数了数是21件
We actually counted 21.
-什么 -对
- Excuse me? - Yeah.
我也是 数了21件
Same here, 21 bodies.
不 不 那太扯了
Oh, no, no, that's ridiculous.
不 不 我有文件
No, no, no. I have the paperwork
在这 Gibbs探员
right here, Agent Gibbs.
你的人肯定数错了
Clearly your people miscounted.
或者这里的某具尸体不属于这里
Or one of these bodies doesn't belong.
我们再查查
We'll check.
黑杰克 也被称为21点
Blackjack, also known as 21.
21响礼炮 21岁是可以赌博的年级
21-gun salute. 21 is the gambling age.
也是可以喝酒的年纪 根据一项被
It's also the drinking age, and according to a study
医学界广泛反驳的研究表明
which is widely dismissed by the medical community,
人类的灵魂重达21克
the human soul weighs 21 grams.
Jim医生 有何发现
Dr. Jim, what do we know?
21其实是文化中很重要的一个数字
21 was a culturally significant number.
对他而言尤其重要 你知道身份了么
Significant for him. You got an ID?
我刚把指纹送到Kasie那里了
I just sent the prints up to Kasie,
不过这个尸体是那堆尸体中唯一一个
but since this body was the only body without a toe tag
没有标牌和任何正当文件的
or any proper paperwork for cadavers...
不是医学尸体
Not a cadaver.
还好有NCIS在那里记数
Good thing NCIS was there to count.
这个尸体内部温度
This man did have an internal core temperature
有75华氏度
【注：大约23.9摄氏度】
of 75 degrees.
-所以他是最近才死的 -对 很可能是昨晚
- So his time of death was recent. - Yeah, last night-ish.
没有看出明显死因
There's no obvious signs of a cause of death,
但是他眼睛里还有鼻子 喉咙
though there's some slight discoloration
有一些轻微的变色
in his eyes, as well as his nose, throat.
吸入了什么坏东西么
Breathed something bad?
也许吧 他肯定不是老死的
Maybe. He certainly didn't die of old age.
我猜他大概不到三十岁吧
I'd put him in his late 20s.
有伤疤 胎记么
Any scars, any markings?
没 没什么标志性的标记
No, no, nothing outwardly identifying,
所以我们得看看里面
which is why we must look inward.
最好退后几步
Might want to step back.
那肯定不对头 因为没有什么法律
That has to be wrong because there are no laws
能不允许在舞厅里面摆尸体
against bodies in ballrooms.
显然 确实有这么一回事 你读读
Apparently, it's a thing. Read.
对于未注册的医学尸体有很多相关法律
There are many laws about unregistered cadavers.
我们还继续约会吗
那这哥们儿是哪里冒出来的呢
So where did this guy come from?
我们还继续约会吗
那这哥们儿是哪里冒出来的呢
So where did this guy come from?
我希望能找出原因
I'm hopefully about to find out.
抱歉 得忙工作
这就怪了
Oh. Oh, that's odd.
-什么意思 -尸体中没有肺
- What're we looking at? - A body without lungs.
它们都被
They have completely...
完全分解了
disintegrated.
哇偶 等等
Whoa, whoa. Hold up.
你问都没问就取消了Bishop的约会吗
So you did cancel Bishop's date without asking?
没有 我就是 我就说了句 “抱歉啊 得忙工作”
No, I just, all I said was, uh, uh, "Sorry, work stuff,"
因为 你看 她工作太忙就没回复
because, you know, she was too busy working to reply.
听上去确实是取消了约会
Sounds like you cancelled.
我们是不是跑题了
Maybe we're getting off topic?
你也没时间了
And you're running out of time.
我手机马上就响 告诉我
My phone's gonna ring, telling me
媒体见面会就要开始了
the press conference is about to start.
媒体见面会
Press conference?
两个NCIS探员被逮捕了
Two NCIS agents are being arrested.
我得争取舆论上的主动
I have to get ahead of this.
所以我猜某人马上就要讲到重点了
So I suggest someone get to the damn point.
那人肯定是Tim
That'd be Tim.
我当时不在解剖室
I wasn't in autopsy,
但后来我们的法医科学家
but I was in the bullpen later
来汇报消息的时候 我正在职员办公大厅里
when our forensic scientist came in with news.
嘿
Hey.
-嘿 -哇
- Hey. - Whoa.
-这什么时候到这的 -哦
- When did this get here? - Oh.
邮车刚来放下的 这次你又订了什么
Uh, mail cart just came by. What did you order this time?
什么 你开玩笑么 Splendifida的东西
What, are you kidding? I can't afford anything
我哪买得起啊
from Splendifida.
但是他们做的东西确实不错
But they do make nice stuff.
你确定没有疯狂购物吗
You're sure you didn't gadget splurge?
也许是梦游剁手
Maybe in your sleep?
不可能 Delilah每天11点半之后都会封锁信用卡通道
No, Delilah blocked all credit card access after 11:30 p.m.
确实是寄给我的 怪了
It is addressed to me. Weird.
拦住媒体
Stop the presses.
别挂机
Hold the phone.
也别跑
And the horses.
我刚得到了咱们解剖室尸体的
I just got the results back
搜索结果
from our body in autopsy,
我们已经回溯了时光
and we have traveled back in time.
-那是好是坏啊 -坏
- Is that good or bad? - Bad.
你看过科幻电影么
Have you ever watched a science-fiction movie?
空间时间的统一性决不能被干扰
The space-time continuum should never be disrupted.
你知道死因了么
You got a cause of death.
把时间拨回一战时期
Set the wayback machine for World War I.
我们神秘尸体的肺
The lungs in our mystery body have disintegrated
是由于暴露在有毒氯气中才发生了分解
from exposure to toxic chlorine gas.
这种毒气是以战争犯罪被日内瓦公约所禁止了的
The kind banned by the Geneva Convention as a war crime.
被害者是被
Victim was killed
化学武器杀害
by a chemical weapon.
穿越时光不是好事儿啊
Time travel is always bad.
-当心 -哦
- Heads up. - Oh.
好了 氯气 太坏了
Okay. Chlorine gas. That's bad.
但是我已经知道这一个受害者了 到现在为止
But I already knew about this one victim. And, so far,
我还没见到任何证据表明
I haven't seen any evidence to suggest
有更大的恐怖威胁
a greater threat of terrorism.
我们知道了消失的毒气
We know about the missing gas.
啥
I'm sorry?
失踪的那批化学武器
The missing batch of chemical weapons?
足够毒死一整个城市街区的人
Enough to poison an entire city block.
他们在说什么
What are they talking about?
更大的恐怖威胁
"A greater threat of terrorism."
我们有一具神秘死尸
We had a mystery dead body
是被氯气杀死的 这很糟糕
killed by chlorine gas. That's bad.
但是到Kasie进来并生动形象地给我们上了一课之前
But we didn't know how bad until Kasie came in
我们都不知道这有多糟糕
and, well, gave a very moving presentation.
我 我在展示之前需要休息一会
I, uh, I'm gonna need a minute before my presentation.
你还好么
You okay?
我很好 只是 得歇一歇
Totally. Just, uh, need a beat.
-嗯 -哥们 这都什么东西啊
- Hmm. - Yeah, dude. What is all this stuff?
无人机 VR眼镜 瞧这个
Drones, VR goggles, oh, check this out.
这是他们冬季风格目录里面的
This is from their winter style catalogue.
是个腕表
It's a wristwatch.
有一个隐藏的摄像机和隐藏的小刀
It's got a hidden camera and a hidden knife.
-隐藏小刀 -对
- A hidden knife? - Yeah.
哇
Whoa.
-我喜欢隐藏的小刀 -嗯
- I like hidden knives. - Yeah.
这都是免费的么
Was all this stuff free?
我上个月给那公司发了邮件
You know, I e-mailed the company last month.
可能是因为我发现了什么 用户界面的小问题
It must be because I pointed some, uh, U.I. glitches
还有 我最新机器小狗里面的软件bug
and software bugs on my new robotic dog.
这是给双胞胎的圣诞礼物
It's a Christmas gift for the twins.
对 当然
Yeah, of course.
好了 我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready.
氯气是在1915年由Fritz Haber制造出来的
Chlorine gas was developed in 1915 by Fritz Haber.
主要是用来绕过自动推进
It was mainly to get around a treaty
武器的禁止条约
prohibiting the use of projectiles.
氯气贴着地面扩散
Chlorine hovers at ground level
呈现为黄绿色的云状 闻起来有菠萝和胡椒的味道
in yellow-green clouds that smell like pineapple and pepper.
还会混入肺部
And melt lungs.
纯粹的邪恶 真的 所以 自然的
Pure evil, really. So, of course,
美国和俄国在冷战期间制造了成吨的氯气
the U.S. and Russia developed tons of it during the Cold War.
说实在的 人类有时候真挺差劲的
You know, humans can really suck sometimes.
所以我们才要用外交手段
Which is why we have diplomacy.
化学武器后来被禁止了 地球上和平了
Chemical weapons have since been banned. Peace on Earth.
如果化学武器已经被禁止了
So if chemicals have been banned,
那我们这死者是怎么死的
how did our dead guy get dead?
因为它们还没有被全部销毁
Because they haven't all been destroyed yet.
销毁过程费钱又费时间
Destruction is expensive and slow.
美国的储备直到2023年才会被完全消除
The U.S. stockpile won't be eliminated until 2023,
会花费大概500亿美元
at a cost of around $50 billion.
-但这还不是让人沮丧的部分 -这还不是
- But that's not the depressing part. - It's not?
化学武器还在被使用
Chemical weapons are still in use.
一份联合国报告谴责叙利亚政府
A U.N. report condemned the Syrian government
于去年向他们自己的人民投掷氯气炸弹
for dropping chlorine bombs on its own people last year,
包括平民和儿童
including civilians and children.
我无法想象
I can't imagine.
我们能聊点愉快的事情吗
Can we talk about something happier?
哦
Oh.
噢 太好了 我们这个损毁严重的
Oh, yay. Fingerprints came back
神秘尸体的指纹结果出来了
on our grossly disfigured mystery body.
快乐到此为止了
So much for happier.
我不敢相信Keenan死了
I can't believe Keenan's dead.
Grant小姐  你和你弟弟
Miss Grant, uh, when was
最后一次谈话是在什么时候
the last time you spoke to your brother?
上周
Last week.
Keenan是我们家族里唯一一个
Keenan was the only one in our family who was actually
实际上在做好事的人
on his way to making good,
现在他这个蠢货赔上了性命
and now he got his stupid ass killed.
-你怪罪你弟弟 -我就是在怪罪他
- You blame your brother. - You're damn right I do.
妈妈死了之后 他向我保证不会丢下我独自一人
After Mom died, he promised me he wouldn't leave me alone.
我们想问你一些
We'd like to ask you a few questions
关于他工作的问题 在
about his job at, uh...
他打两份工
He worked two jobs.
他在我当厨师的那个
He was a busboy
鬼地方打杂 但是他的另一份工作
at the hellhole I cook at, but the other one
是在一个好公司的不错的工作
was a good job at a nice company.
三源化学药剂销毁工厂
Trine Chemical Agent Destruction Plant.
Keenan是我们家族里
Keenan was the only one in our family
唯一一个能通过他们要求的背景审查的人
who could actually pass the required background check.
他从没有过犯罪记录
He never had a criminal record.
我们认为他的工作可能和他的死亡有一定的关系
We think that his job might have something to do with his death.
-他是给他们开卡车的 -他提到过氯气吗
- He was driving trucks for them. - He ever mention chlorine?
他的工作包括处理危险的东西吗
Did his job include handling anything dangerous?
如果你想了解化学相关的 去和那家公司谈
If you want to know about chemicals, talk to the company.
我们也在做 但是
We are. But...
Keenan没有把事情搞砸
Keenan didn't screw up.
我可以指责我的弟弟 你们不能
I get to blame my baby brother. You don't.
这地方跟诺克斯堡似得
This place is like Fort Knox.
当然 化学物品也可能和黄金一样值钱
Well, chemicals can be just as valuable as gold.
当然也更加危险
Certainly more dangerous.
我在想是谁在看着 看到那个了吗
I wonder who's watching. See there?
你好 打扰一下
Hi. Excuse me.
你们一定是NCIS的人了
You must be NCIS.
抱歉来的太晚了 我是一路穿过整个厂区走过来的
My apologies for being so late. I was all the way across campus.
而且 他们给了我们这种高尔夫球车
And, uh, they give us these golf carts,
但为什么要浪费能源呢 对吧 我是Patton Hartgrave博士
but why waste the energy, right? Dr. Patton Hartgrave.
你好 也是三源的首席化学工程师
Hi. Trine's lead chemical engineer.
那么
So...
抱歉
Excuse me.
如果你们不担心看上去显得太笨的话
If you, uh, aren't afraid to look too dorky,
我可以带你参观一下
I could show you around.
我绝不可能看上去笨笨的
It's impossible for me to look dorky.
你说是就是吧
Right.
这里就是见证奇迹的地方
So this is where the magic happens.
我们用两种方式处理有害的化学品
We dispose of harmful chemicals two ways: incineration
焚烧和中和 混入其他试剂
and neutralization, mixing in other agents
来消除毒性
to eliminate toxicity.
都是非常有效 非常安全的
It's all very effective, very safe.
这也意味着昂贵的花费
Which means it's very expensive.
我向你保证每一分钱都是值得的
Well, I can assure you it's worth every penny.
Keenan Grant在哪儿工作
Where did Keenan Grant work?
好吧
Right.
这个 这个是Grant先生的储物柜
This is, uh... this is Mr. Grant's locker.
我和他本人不熟
I didn't know him personally,
但是当然了 我们听到了发生的事情时都很震惊
but of course, we're all very shocked to hear what happened.
两个晚上之前他在工作吗
Was he working two nights ago?
呃 让我们看看
Uh, let's see.
实际上 我有权查看那些记录
Actually, I have access to those records.
呣
Mm...
哦 是的 看起来他那天晚上是在工作
Uh, yes. It looks like he was working that night.
是去特区的佛蒙特旅馆取货
It was a single pickup at the Freemont Inn in D.C.
那里也是他的尸体被发现的地方
That's where his body was found.
他是要去取什么货
What was he picking up?
一些用于再循环的工业塑料
Some industrial plastic for recycling.
不是什么危险品
It's nothing too dangerous.
是酒店的垃圾 又不是去切尔诺贝利
It's hotel waste, not Chernobyl, which...
那是个没人当回事的生态警示
was an ecological warning sign nobody took seriously enough.
你作为一个化学家似乎
You seem very, uh, Earth-friendly
很关心地球生态保护
for a chemical guy.
嘿 我只是在纠正人类犯下的一些最糟的错误之一
Hey, I'm just correcting some of mankind's worst mistakes.
比如销毁氯气
Like destroying chlorine gas.
那时不可能的
That's impossible.
噢 呃 McGee探员和Torres探员 这位是George Ashley Green
Oh, uh, Agents McGee and Torres, this is George Ashley Green,
我们无畏的领导
our fearless leader.
而且也是三源化学的首席执行官
Well, CEO of Trine Chemical, anyway.
我刚好看到你们两个进来了
I happened to see you two come in.
我就知道有人在盯着
I knew somebody was watching.
为什么毁掉氯气是不可能的
Why is destroying chlorine gas impossible?
因为我们多年都没有氯气了
Because we haven't had any for years.
按照之前每次的军事合同
It was all destroyed per previous
都全部处理掉了
military contracts.
当前的合同呢
What about current contracts?
没有和氯气相关的
None, for chlorine.
但没有许可我也只能说这么多了
But that's all I can really say without clearance.
这关乎国家安全
National security concerns.
你能理解的
You understand.
我需要五角大楼的批准
I need permission from the Pentagon.
嘿 Bishop 说
Hey, Bishop. Go.
国防部又在
The DoD is pushing
推迟你的会面时间了
your meeting time, again.
实际上 他们取消了会见
Actually, they cancelled
并且建议你明天再来
and suggested you come back tomorrow.
噢 不 不 不 不
Oh, no. No, no, no.
在得到一些答复之前我是不会走的
I'm not going anywhere until I get some answers.
我跟他们也是这么说的 但他们一直重复
That's what I told them, but they kept citing
这关乎国家安全而不说什么详情
"national security concerns" without any details.
呃 Bishop
Uh, Bishop?
我之后再联系你
I'll call you back.
下午好
Good afternoon.
特别探员Gibbs 对吗
Special Agent Gibbs, right?
Wynn Crawford
Wynn Crawford.
-是的 先生 -我刚和海军部长
- Yes, sir. - I just got done
聊过你的队伍
talking about your team with SECNAV.
她讲了不少关于你的故事 都是好事
She had quite a few stories about you, all good.
-我想也是 -关于你的会面
- I'll bet. - About your meeting...
-呃 被取消了 -是我取消的
- Uh, it was cancelled. - By me.
但既然你在这里了 我想
But since you're here, I figured
我还是当面告诉你这个坏消息吧
I'd give you the bad news in person.
五角大楼的记录已经被临时封锁了
Pentagon records have been temporarily locked.
-被你封锁的 -不 是政府部门
- By you. - No, by State.
他们目前正在和联合国合作
They're currently working with the U.N.
达成关于叙利亚的停火协议
on a cease-fire agreement in Syria.
你的请求传递出了危险信息
Your requests sent up red flags.
化学武器的调查让人们很紧张
Chemical weapons investigations make people nervous.
化学袭击也一样
So do chemical attacks.
没错 你瞧 这正是我们
Yeah, see, that's exactly
无法承担的不计后果的谈话
the kind of reckless talk that we can't afford.
现在 你有证据表明存在
Now, do you have proof
有预期的恐怖主义活动吗
of intended terrorism?
还是有武器失踪
Or missing weapons?
你让找证据变得困难了
You're making it hard to find proof.
那你就换种方式找证据 我会很高兴提供帮助的
Well, find a different way, and I'll be happy to help.
我想为你们的受害者寻求正义
I want justice for your victim.
但是陆战队员之间 我说个真话
But Marine to Marine?
世界舞台上 这会儿还有很多更大的事情正在发生
There are a lot bigger things at play here on the world stage.
我们可以两者兼顾的 部长先生
We can do both, Mr. Secretary.
我说这些只是出于礼貌 而不是跟你讨价还价
This was a courtesy, not a negotiation.
现在 除非NCIS
Now, unless NCIS
有确凿证据证明武器失踪了 我说的是真正意义上的武器
has concrete evidence of missing weapons-- actual weapons--
否则 你们就要停止行动
you will stand down.
这是命令
That's an order.
所以 Gibbs把我让你们停止行动的命令
So, Gibbs told you about my order
告诉了你们 然而你们依然没有服从
to stand down, and you still failed to follow it.
我自己也经常不同意Gibbs的做法 长官
I don't always agree with Gibbs myself, sir,
但是我相信他的判断
but I do trust his judgment,
还有我NCIS的同事们的判断
and the judgment of my people here at NCIS.
如果他们没有服从你的命令 那是因为
If they didn't follow your order, it's because
确实有武器失踪了
there are missing weapons.
而这个坐在审讯室里的化学工程师
And the chemical engineer sitting in interrogation...
-他会告诉我们一切吗 -继续看
- Can tell us everything? - Keep watching.
我的人知道怎么击溃他
My people know how to break this guy.
我什么都不说
I'm not saying a word,
所以要么逮捕我 要么放我走
so just arrest me or be done.
很抱歉
I'm sorry,
我们耽误你什么事儿了吗
are we keeping you from something?
你还有约会什么的吗
Hot date, maybe?
哦 天哪
Oh, God!
露馅了
Cat's out of the bag.
我想你们可以说我跟大地母亲有个约会
Guess you could say my hot date's with Mother Earth.
约会地点是地下的棺材里面
Six feet under.
你之前被暴露在毒气中了
You were exposed to the gas.
剂量不多 但是足够致死了
Not much, but enough.
我会在你们逼我交代之前死掉
I'll be dead before you can get me to talk.
我去拿急救箱
I'll get the kit.
抱歉
Sorry.
我猜 NCIS已经没什么能做的了
Well, I guess NCIS is done here.
你需要医疗救护
You need medical attention.
我们正在呼叫医疗人员
We're calling the paramedics.
不 已经太晚了
No, no, no, it's too late for that.
我说过我不想接受急救
I told you I don't want that.
这个人正在咳血
The fact that this man is coughing up blood
这就意味着我们是对的
means that we are right.
长官 现在依然有很多遗失的氯气
Sir, there is missing chlorine gas,
这个人知道氯气在哪
and this man knows where it is.
你们又是怎么发现的
And you found this out how?
你们好像忘记了故事里面
You seem to have forgotten the part of the story
你们俩违反了联邦法律的部分
where you two committed a federal offense.
实际上 如果我不了解情况的话
In fact, if I didn't know any better,
我会说你们是在故意拖延时间
I'd say you're deliberately stalling.
-完全没有 -不可能
- Not at all. - No way.
约会习惯 短信息 免费的小玩意儿
Dating habits, text messages, free gadgets.
这些难道是你们NCIS的工作日常吗
These are all essential to your work here at NCIS?
实际上 没错
Actually, yeah.
-嘿 Nick -怎么了
- Hey, Nick. - What up?
是你取消了我昨晚的约会吗
Did you cancel my date last night?
早上好
Good morning.
我昨晚应该出去约会的
I was supposed to have a date last night,
但是据Boyd所说 我把约会取消了
but according to Boyd, I cancelled it.
你没跟我商量
You sent a message
-就发了信息 -Gibbs当时就站在那里
- without telling me. - Gibbs was standing right there.
你想让我怎么做 让你陷入麻烦吗
What do you want me to do, let you get in trouble?
就为了条信息吗
For getting a text message?
这根本说不过去
That doesn't make any sense.
他甚至不知道信息是谁发的
He didn't even know who it was from.
没错 而且他对这事儿没兴趣
Yeah, he didn't care, either.
五角大楼的记录 什么情况了
Pentagon records. Go.
我们依然没有访问文件的许可
Well, we still don't have permission to access files.
要想找到失踪的武器
In order to find missing chemical weapons,
我们得黑进五角大楼
we're gonna have to hack into the Pentagon,
而这有点小风险
which is a little risky.
还是违法的
And a lot illegal.
-另找个方法 -我们可能有另外的办法了
- Find a different way. - We may already have.
退而求其次的话 Torres和我能查到另外的文件
Torres and I are able to access the next best thing.
Trine化学公司自己的记录
Records to Trine Chemical itself.
额 等等 Nick帮你搞黑客行动吗
Uh, I'm sorry. Nick is helping you hack?
当然了
Hell yeah.
-嗯 -当然 是用我的方式
- Hmm. - Well, in my own way.
这里有一个隐藏摄像头 在那个公司里的时候
There was a hidden camera, and it was recording the entire time
-全程进行了录像 -其中包括了Hartgrave
- while we were at the company. - Including when Hartgrave
-输入他管理员密码的时候 -只是意外而已
-entered his admin password. - It was by accident.
弗吉尼亚州是一个一致同意允许录像的州
Virginia is a one-party consent state for recording.
你追踪到他的按键动作了吗
You tracked his keystrokes?
我们确实有一个跟我们受害者 Keenan Grant有关的
We do have a warrant for security records
允许查看安全记录的搜查令
pertaining to our victim, Keenan Grant.
这可不包括化学武器记录
Which doesn't cover records of chemical weapons.
-所以我不会下载那些记录 -不会故意下载
- So we don't download those. -On purpose.
那国防部长关于停止行动的命令呢
What about SecDef's order to stand down?
老大
Boss?
做吧 McGee
Do it, McGee.
好的 我建议你尽快下载
All right, well, I suggest you download as much as you can
尽量多的信息
as fast as you can.
为什么
Why?
一个规模这么大的公司会有追踪
A company this big has security protocols
外部IP的安全协议
tracing outside IPs.
所以我编了一个程序
Which is why I created a program
来警告我
that'll alert me if I...
哦
Ooh.
警告我我被追踪了
Alert me if I'm being traced.
-他们找到你了吗 -问错了问题
- Did they find you? - Wrong question.
你拿到文件了吗
Did you get the file?
幸运的是 我成功地
Well, luckily, I was able to
对下载直接进行了安全备份
directly download to a secure backup.
只需要找台电脑打开它
Just need someone's computer to open it.
那是我们的受害者
There's our victim
他死亡的那天夜里
the night of his death.
他那天晚上在工作
He was working that night.
等一下 我们的科学家也在那里
Hold up. So was our scientist.
他跟我们撒了谎
He lied to us.
为什么首席工程师随便上了一个卡车
Why would the lead engineer go on a random pickup?
除非那个卡车上有什么非常重要的东西
Unless there was something very valuable on that truck.
-比如氯气 -Hartgrave是凶手吗
- Like chlorine? - Is Hartgrave our killer?
是时候问一下了 我去找Gibbs
It's time to ask. I'll get Gibbs.
没必要
No need.
主任
Director.
Gibbs
Gibbs.
我刚接到Trine化学公司的电话
I just received a call from Trine Chemical.
实际上 打电话的是他们的网络安全部门
Their cyber security department, actually.
NCIS有没有犯下非法进行黑客行为的重罪
Did NCIS just participate in a felony by hacking?
额 这更像是法律的灰色地带  长官
It's, uh, it's more of a gray area, sir.
这可不好
This is bad.
Torres和McGee应该干些什么
What are Torres and McGee supposed to do?
陈述事实
Tell the truth.
这很糟 对吧
Yeah, that's bad, right?
Hartgrave 他在哪
Hartgrave. Where is he?
根据公司保安的说法 他刚刚打卡进去了
According to company security, he just clocked in.
好的 我们走
Okay, let's go.
好吧 也许没那么糟
Okay. Maybe it's not that bad.
那是国防部长
That's the United States Secretary of Defense.
-我们走 -他现在提供上门服务了吗
- Let's go. - He's making house calls now?
这很糟
Yeah. It's bad.
然后就是现在的处境了
Which brings us to now.
所以 就像你看到的
So, as you can see,
那个科学家在是否在现场和毒气的事情上撒了谎
our scientist lied about being there and the gas.
是的 没错 我看见了
Yes. Yes, I do see.
我还看到应该要求Gibbs探员应该为
I also see the need to ask for Agent Gibbs' badge
允许他的探员们违反多项法律交出他的徽章
for allowing his agents to break so many laws.
NCIS有搜查令 长官
NCIS had a warrant, sir.
而且担心走传统程序去接近Hartgrave的话 他会
And a reasonable fear that Hartgrave could alter records
篡改记录 这个担心非常合理
if traditionally approached.
所以 这是个精明的电脑策略
Hence the shrewd computer tactics.
-没错 -是的 就像他说的
- Exactly. - Yeah, what he said.
你们窃取政府记录
You stole government records.
我们证明了Hartgrave确实在那里
We proved that Hartgrave was there.
就在一切开始的地方 跟失踪的氯气在一起
At ground zero, with the missing chlorine.
我们必须假设 它会被用来进行袭击
We have to assume it's going to be used for an attack.
长官 这个人知道所有细节
Sir, this guy knows all the details.
NCIS能够击垮他
NCIS is going to break him.
我们是需要更多的时间
We just need more time.
说得太对了
Damn Skippy.
急救人员在路上了
Medical's on the way.
我不要他们的帮忙
I won't accept their help.
为什么 Patton
Why not, Patton?
因为羞愧
Is it shame?
还是有负罪感
Guilt?
有人死了
A man's dead.
而你在这里
And you were there.
我们知道你在受害人死的那个晚上
We have you with the victim
和他一起
the night of his death and at the hotel
待在发现他尸体的酒店
where his body was found.
他发现了你偷氯气 是吗
He found out you stole the chlorine, right?
-你杀了他 -不是的
- You killed him. - No.
我
I...
"我"怎么了 说完啊
"I..." Come on, finish the sentence.
我是凶手
"I am a murderer."
快点 对你所做的事负责
Aw, come on, man. Own it.
Keenan的死是个意外
Keenan's death was an accident.
我试着救他
I tried to save him.
-在发现你的时候吗 -是的
- That's when you were exposed? - Yes.
我想要安全地卸下氯
I was going to unload the chlorine safely...
从卡车上吗
From the truck?
我不可能
It's not like I could
把我的车开到装卸码头
back my car up to the loading dock.
但是
But, uh...
我们到了酒店后 Keenan发现了那个箱子
...when we got to the hotel, Keenan, he found the crate
他打开了 我来不及阻止
and opened it before I could stop him.
他的撬棍肯定滑落了 或者
His crowbar must have slipped, or--
当我关闭阀门时，他已经死了
He was dead by the time I closed the valve.
你看到了医学遗体 把他的尸体藏到这中间
You saw the medical cadavers and hid the body.
等等
Wait,
那个好人在完成自己的工作
a good man was doing his job,
而你却没有负罪感吗
and you don't feel guilt?
我有 在那件事上
I do, about that.
但是偷能杀死无数人的化学武器
Oh, but stealing barbaric chemical weapons
就没什么问题吗
that could kill hundreds, you're cool with that?
偷 是啊 你怎么能够偷
Steal. Right. How can you steal
根本不在我们记录上的东西呢
something that wasn't even in our records?
我在仓库里发现了这些罐子
I found the canisters in the vault.
并且拿走了它们
And took them.
他们不会错过它的
They weren't gonna miss it.
氯气在哪里
Where's the gas?
我想要相信
You know, I wanted to believe that
我在为世界上的许多错误
I was doing my part
做出一些平和的改正
to peacefully right a few wrongs in this world.
这不够
It wasn't enough.
恶魔不停进攻
Evil plays offense.
是啊 现在你也是这样了
Right. So now you are, too.
不是我
Not me.
不是我 是受到政府氯气威胁的市民们
No, the citizens being gassed by their own government.
他们需要一种强大的武器
They need a weapon just as strong.
我们将阿富汗人武装起来去对抗俄罗斯人 不是吗
We armed the Afghans against the Russians, right?
或者是80年代尼加拉瓜叛乱中的)反桑地诺主义者
Or what about the Contras in the '80s?
氯气在哪里
Where is the gas?!
在送给自由战士的路上
On its way to freedom fighters.
他们知道我想要完成的事情
They understand what I'm trying to accomplish.
你看过那些孩子死亡的视频吗
Have you seen the videos of those kids dying?
请听我说
Please listen to me.
你认为的高尚会导致
Your supposed nobility is gonna get
更多人的死亡 -不会的
a lot more people killed. - No.
不会的 一旦到了叙利亚
No, the gas will be in good hands...
会有人保管好它们
...once it gets to Syria.
恐怖组织的成员
Members of terrorist organizations
知道你加入了自由战士
have been known to join your freedom fighters
来获得情报或者偷得武器
to gain Intel or to steal weapons.
你不知道这些气体会用在哪里 是吗
You don't know where the gas will end up, do you?
关于这些东西的消息传得到处都是
Word about these kind of things gets around.
坏人从暗中出现
Bad guys come out of the woodwork.
不是的 事情已经发生了
No. What's done is done.
你有什么想法 Ellie
I hope you have some ideas, Ellie.
我不知道该怎么接近他
I don't know how to reach this guy.
他会承认一切
Well, he'll admit to everything,
但不会放弃气体
but won't give up the gas.
你不能和疯子争执
You can't argue with crazy.
他不是个疯子
Oh, he's not crazy.
他有原则
He's principled.
他就是这么认为的
That's how he sees it.
他上一次行动完全就是正义的
His last act on earth is totally righteous.
除非那不是 不过那时他就会死了
Until it's not, but by then, he'll be dead.
我们需要更多的时间
We need more time.
不行 没有更多时间了 主任
No, no more time, Director.
外面有遗失的气体
There's missing gas out there.
长官 我们一直在说这个
Sir, that's what we've been saying.
更有理由把这件事尽快交给国土安全部
All the more reason to turn it over to Homeland
和FBI处理了
and the FBI as soon as possible.
对于Gibbs探员和他的队伍来说
As far as Agent Gibbs and his team are concerned,
他们将在法庭上度过一天
they'll get their day in court.
-我们会小心行事的 -我才
- We'll be discreet. - I don't give a damn
不关心出镜这件事 长官
about appearances, sir.
化学武器流落在外
There are chemical weapons out there.
你却要浪费时间交接案子
And you want to waste time transferring the case
主要嫌犯还在我们面前
when the lead suspect is-- is right in front of us.
-记者会马上要开始了 -我有个注意
- That press conference is ready to begin. - I have an idea.
-我也有个 你的是什么 -还有什么事吗
- Me, too. What's yours? - Anything else?
Crawford部长 你正在犯一个大错误
Secretary Crawford, you are making a big mistake.
正是我想的那样
That's what I was thinking.
你是对的 错误就是在这里浪费时间
You're right, but the mistake is wasting time in here.
Torres探员 你究竟在做些什么
Agent Torres, what the hell are you doing?
对啊 你在做什么
Yeah, what are you doing?
等等 那不是你的主意吗
Wait, this wasn't your idea?
不是 我的主意是系统验证模式
No, SCIF mode was my idea.
那你为什么看着我放在桌上的枪
Then why did you look at my gun on the table?
我没看你的枪
I wasn't looking at your gun.
Vance主任
Director Vance,
你的探员们是在威胁
are your agents threatening
美国国防部长吗
the United States Secretary of Defense?
我当然不希望是这样的
I certainly hope not.
你挟持我每多20分钟
I figure every 20 minutes you hold me hostage,
你的徒刑就会增加一年
there's another year on your sentence.
是吗 等等 挟持
Huh? Wait, what? Hostage?
那就是你做的事 不是吗
Well, that's what you're doing, isn't it?
不不不
No. No, no, no.
不是
Not at all.
系统验证模式切断了手机信号
Well, SCIF mode cuts cell service...
而你又装备了武器
and you're armed.
哦 这个啊
Oh-- Oh, this?
哦不 这个 还是个皮套子
Oh, no, this is, uh, it's still holstered.
我们只是要求多点时间 长官
Yeah, we-we're merely asking for more time, sir.
你们的嫌犯不会再说什么了 他已经明确了
Your suspect isn't gonna talk. He's made that quite clear.
我告诉过你们 我不需要医疗救助
I told you, I don't want any medical help.
嘿
Hey!
我要打电话
I want my phone call!
我 我 想和我妈妈说话
I... I-- geez, I want to talk to my mom.
安全锁定 继续锁定
Security lockdown on... Going on lockdown.
第一批应急人员已到现场
We got first responders on the ground...
不行
No.
Bishop不行 停下
Bishop, no. Stop, stop.
呆在那里 不行
You stay there. No!
继续告诉我消息
Y-You keep me informed.
发生什么了
Hey. What's-what's going on?
出什么事了
Is something wrong?
当局赶到现场
Authorities are just arriving on the scene.
拆弹组和危险品处理小组已经进入大楼
Metro bomb squad and Hazmat teams have entered the building.
联邦当局刚发布了官方声明
While federal authorities have yet to issue a formal statement,
警方要求特区地区的市民
police are asking everyone in the greater D.C. area
呆在家中
to remain in their homes.
你的气体被用在了袭击事件中
Your gas was used in an attack.
这是WJGZ节目先前收到的
Again, here is the footage WJGZ received earlier,
用手机拍摄的视频
taken with a cell phone.
这段视频年龄较小的观众不宜观看
This video may not be suitable for younger viewers.
快走 快走 快走
Go, go, go!
不 这说不通
No. This doesn't make any sense.
-当然说不通 -这是恐怖袭击
- Of course it doesn't. - It's terrorism!
这说明你的上个行动
Which means your last act on Earth
会杀死无辜民众
will be the killing of innocent people.
那和你的基石相符吗
Think that'll fit on your headstone?
-我是信的 -不不 那不是
- I'll make sure it does. - No, no. That's not...
那不是我
That's-that's not what I...
那你再找出个人来让我们责备
Well, then, you give me someone else to blame!
我把箱子给了一个海关探员
Uh, okay, uh, I-I gave the crate to a customs agent.
地址
Address.
他不知道里面有什么
Uh, he didn't know what was inside.
他一定打开过
He must have opened it.
Leon 那是我想的那样吧
Leon, is this what I think it is?
我要完蛋了
I'll be damned.
-我已获知... -闭路电视5频道
-I'm now being told... - Closed circuit, channel five.
酒店已经被疏散 紧急救援部门
the hotel has been evacuated, and that emergency services
正继续在该地展开...
are continuing to fan out throughout the area...
嘿 呃 谢谢你 Ross先生
Hey, uh, thank you. Thank you, Mr. Ross,
不过你可以不用读了
but you can stop reading now.
呃 稿子到这里结束了 所以我即兴创作了最后一段
The, uh, script ended, so I improvised that last part.
-我希望没啥问题 -Bishop探员给我发了消息
- I hope that was okay. - Agent Bishop texted me.
你简直棒极了
You were perfect.
部长 主任
Mr. Secretary, Mr. Director.
非常感谢你允许我
Thank you so much for allowing me
成为你们军事演习的一部分
to be a part of your operations drill.
我 我得说 这对我来说是个全新的任务
I, uh, have to say, this was a new one for me.
是啊 对我们来说也是
Yeah. Us, too.
Hines小姐 这个广播节目
Miss Hines, this broadcast
只通过闭路电视播出了 对吗
was only sent via closed circuit, right?
-是的 只在我们大楼里 主任 -那些镜头
- Yes. Our building only, Director. - The footage,
-到处逃跑的人们 -呃那些研讨会上的
- the running people. - Uh, the agents
探员们愿意提供帮助
at the seminar, they were happy to help.
我们告诉他们这是一个 执法舆情学 的演练
We told them it was an exercise in "Optics In Law Enforcement."
尸体都是真的尸体
And the bodies were the cadavers.
并不是那样 长官
Not exactly, sir,
不过我喜欢你那么想
but I like where your head is at.
我很抱歉 部长先生
I'm so sorry, uh, Mr. Secretary.
该死的Gibss哪儿去了
Where the hell is Gibbs?
联邦探员
Federal agents.
嘿 举起手来
Hey, put your hands in the air.
离那个集装箱远一点
Back away from the container.
啊 没啥问题
Oh, looks good.
警报解除 没有泄露
All clear, six-eight.
哇哦 这些很老旧了吧
Wow. These are old, huh?
他们为什么不销毁呢
Why weren't they destroyed?
回收那些毒气并不能开脱NCIS的责任
Recovering that gas does not absolve NCIS.
除了不遵从命令 非法黑客行为
In addition to disobeying orders, illegal hacking
以及威胁政府要员 你还可以加上..
and-and threatening a government official, you can add...
见鬼了 我甚至还不知道该怎么称呼这个局面
well, hell, I don't even know what to call this charade.
这不是胁迫 也不是诱捕
It's not coercion and it's not entrapment.
-没什么用 McGee探员 -我全怪你 Leon
- Not helping, Agent McGee. - And I blame you, Leon.
你就是这样运作你部门的吗 还有那个该死的Gibbs哪儿去了
Is this how you run your house? And where the hell is Gibbs?
在这儿
Right here.
Gibbs 你的警徽也可以丢进这堆了
Gibbs, you can add your badge to the growing pile.
这也给你了
You should have this, too.
那是什么
And what's that?
Trine化工说他们按照军事合同的要求
Trine Chemical said they destroyed all their chlorine,
销毁了全部氯气
per military contracts.
但那都是鬼扯
Well, that's total BS.
是啊 为了省钱他们撒谎了 实际上省了几百万
Yeah, they lied to save a buck. Millions, actually.
我们调查了他们的记录
We went through their records.
你们是非法调查
Illegally obtained.
不 我们有搜查令
No, pretty sure we had a warrant.
当这一切结束时
When this is all over,
-他们公司的股票就会崩溃 -就让他们崩溃啊
- company stock will crash. - Let it.
他们欺骗了美国政府 你想说什么
They defrauded the United States government. Your point?
我想说 长官 你是他们的重要股东
My point, sir, is that you are a major shareholder,
而且你将会损失大量财富
and you stand to lose a lot of money.
你认为我介入是钱的原因
You think I stepped in because of money?
或者是因为你与CEO的友谊
Or your friendship with the CEO.
我从未想到...
I-It never occurred to me that...
在州政府要求我介入时 我不知道Trine卷入其中
I had no idea Trine was involved when State asked me to step in.
放松 我们知道
Relax. We know.
我和George Green好几个月没聊过了
And I haven't talked to George Green in months.
至少这几天确实没有 我们查过了
Certainly not in the last few days. We checked.
天啊 这看起来真糟糕
Geez, this looks bad.
但这并不意味着存在犯罪行为
Doesn't always mean there was a crime.
对吗 主任
Right, Director?
我想NCIS不是唯一一个
I guess NCIS weren't the only ones
抢跑的人
who jumped the gun a little.
在简报
Outside of briefings,
以及偶尔的社交聚会之外
and the occasional social gathering,
我和你互不相识 Leon
you and I don't know each other, Leon.
我做了最坏的打算
I assumed the worst.
我们都会犯错
Well, we all make mistakes.
是啊 就像Bibbs探员和他的团队刚才提醒我的
Yes, as Agent Gibbs and his team have just reminded me.
好吧 如果是这样的话 主任
Well, if that's it, Director,
我要去参加一个新闻发布会
I got a press conference to attend.
长官
Sir?
我得走在前面
I have to get in front of this.
为我的失误负起责任 还要祝贺NCIS完成了他们的任务
Take responsibility for my part, and congratulate NCIS on theirs.
也许下一次
Maybe next time,
我们都会更加谨慎 对吗
we could both be a little more careful. Yeah?
不对
Nope.
干得好
Well done.
-这是你的 -谢谢
- This is yours. - Oh. Thank you.
在这场新闻发布会上
In a news conference addressing this discovery,
美国国防部长Wynn Crawford
United States Secretary of Defense Wynn Crawford
声称对Trine化工的指控
noted that the allegations against Trine Chemical
是一个孤立事件
are an isolated event.
哇哦 一个政客愿意承认他错了
Wow, a politician willing to admit that he was wrong.
-太新奇了 -我知道一切
- It's refreshing. - I knew everything
都会好起来
was gonna be fine.
我一秒都没有怀疑过Gibbs
I never doubted Gibbs one second.
我怀疑了 不过我在适应
I did. But I'm learning.
嘿 Ellie
Hey, Ellie?
嗯
Hmm?
有时间吗
You have a sec?
有 怎么了
Yeah. What's up?
我是想对你的约会道个歉
I just wanted to apologize about your date.
下一次你和Boyd共进晚餐
Next time that Boyd and you go out to dinner,
呃 我来付账
uh, it'll be on me.
谢谢 不过不是因为这个
Thanks, but it's not about that.
好吧
Okay.
我们得信任彼此 Nick
We have to trust each other, Nick,
无论大事还是小事
for the big things and the small things.
这非常重要
It matters.
我犯了个错误 我不该发那条消息
It was a mistake. I shouldn't have sent that text.
那你为什么要发
So why did you?
好吧 晚安 Nick
Okay. Good night, Nick.
Ellie 等等
Ellie, wait.
晚安
Good night.
Kasie 嘿
Kasie, hey.
你 呃 看看这儿有没有想要的东西
Did you, uh, get anything you wanted from here?
这些我不是都需要
'Cause I don't need all this stuff.
噢 没事 我真正想要的
Oh, I'm good. What I really want
是一个他们的数码钟
is one of their Nixie tube clocks.
-噢 那些酷毙了 -我就说嘛 对吧
- Oh, those are cool. - I know, right?
我甚至还联系那个公司 问他们能不能
I even called the company to see what it would take
像你的那样 免费送我一个
to send me one for free, like you.
真的吗
Really?
真的 我提出可以测试他们所有的产品
Yeah, I offered to test all their products
指出缺陷和种种东西
and point out bugs and stuff,
但他们说 他们从来不赠送免费的礼物
but they said they don't send free gift boxes, ever.
他们说 他们只把东西送给
They said they only send goodies
呃 潜在的雇员
to, like, prospective employees.
好吧 我被猎头了
Okay. I'm being headhunted.
是的 是这样
Yeah, you are.
然后呢
And?
然后这个真是棒呆了
And it feels pretty good.
我知道 你要离开NCIS
I knew it. You're gonna leave NCIS
去享受一份性感多金的工作
for a sexy, multimillion dollar job
在全球最酷的科技公司之一
at one of the coolest tech companies in the world.
不不不 我是说 他们承诺给我
No, no, no. I mean, I am-- well, I'm being offered
优厚的待遇 但你知道 实际上
a lot of money, but, uh, you know, really, it's...
不要告诉别人哦
Please don't tell anyone.
我绝对不会告诉任何人 McGee
I would never tell anyone, McGee.
但他们可都是侦探
But they are detectives.
你们都好吗
How y'all doing?
别让那些东西挤占你的头脑
Don't let that stuff go to your head now.
抱歉我来迟了
Sorry I'm late.
你这个职位的人永远不会迟到
Someone in your position is never late.
CIA很惊讶会接到你的电话 长官
CIA was surprised to get your call, sir.
我知道你们正在追踪Leon Vance
I understand you've been tracking Leon Vance.
不知道你在说什么
No idea what you're talking about.
我要知道你得到的一切
I want everything you have.
出于公事还是个人原因
Is this business or pleasure?
这里的鲑鱼怎么样
Now, how's the salmon here?
翻译 素时 42 柒九一九 二噁英 小飞 鸡血
校对  小飞  二噁英
主校 Vincent
分配 鸡血
== sync, corrected by elderman == @elder_man